I'll melt your heart into two
I got that superstar glow so
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
A side step, right-left, to my beat
High like the moon, rock with me, baby
Know that I got that heat
Let me show you, cause talking's cheap
Side step, right-left, to my beat
Get it, let it roll
Smooth like butter
Pull you in like no other
Don't need no Usher
to remind me you got it bad
Ain't no other
that can sweep you up like a robber
Straight up, I got ya
Making you fall like that
Break it down
Ooh, when I look in the mirror
I'll melt your heart into two
I got that superstar glow so
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Side step, right-left, to my beat
High like the moon, rock with me, baby
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Know that I got that heat
Let me show you, cause talking's cheap
Side step right, left to my beat
Get it, let it roll
Ice on my wrist, I'm the nice guy
Got the right body and the right mind
Rollin' up the party, got the right vibes
Smooth like
hate us
Fresh boy, pull up and we lay low
All the players get moving when the bass low
Got army right behind us when we say show
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Let's go
Side step right, left to my beat
Right, left to my beat
High like the moon, rock with me, baby
Know that I got that heat
Let me show you, cause talking's cheap
Side step right, left to my beat
Get it, let it roll
Smooth like
Cool shade
And you know we don't stop
High like
Ain't no
You'll be like, "Oh, my God"
We gon' make you rock, and you say (yeah)
We gon' make you bounce, and you say (yeah)
Hotter, sweeter, cooler, butter
Get it, let it roll