Cause I'm in the stars tonight
So watch me bring the fire and set the night alight
Shoes on get up in the morn
Cup of milk, let's rock and roll
King Kong, kick the drum
rolling on like a rolling stone
Sing song when I'm walkin' home
Jump up to the top LeBron
Ding dong, call me on my phone
Ice tea and a game of ping pong
This is getting heavy
Can you hear the bass boom, I'm ready
Life is sweet as honey
Yeah this beat cha ching like money
Disco overload
I'm into that, I'm good to go
I'm diamond, you know I glow up
So let's go
Cause I'm in the stars tonight
So watch me bring the fire and set the night alight
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
So I'ma light it up like dynamite
Woah-oh-oh
Bring a friend, join the crowd
Whoever wanna come along
Word up, talk the talk
just move like we off the wall
Day or night the sky's alight
So we dance to the break of dawn
Ladies and gentlemen, I got the medicine
so you should keep ya eyes on the ball, huh
This is getting heavy
Can you hear the bass boom, I'm ready
Life is sweet as honey
Yeah this beat cha ching like money
Disco overload
I'm into that, I'm good to go
I'm diamond, you know I glow up
Let's go
Cause I'm in the stars tonight
So watch me bring the fire and set the night alight
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
So I'ma light it up like dynamite
Woah-oh-oh
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na
Life is dynamite
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
So I'ma light it up like dynamite
Woah-oh-oh
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na
Light it up like dynamite
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na
Cause I-I'm in stars tonight
Shining through the city with the little fucking sun
So I'ma light it up like dynamite
So watch me bring the fire, set the night alight
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
So I'ma light it up like dynamite